黑 鏡
終極玩家
字幕組
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
最新最快海外影視字幕下載
翻譯：小酸奶! 杏仁斯嘉麗 章魚埃克斯
校對：草草
時間軸：想念Gallifrey的wholock
后期：吉吉  總監：草草
護照
媽媽來電
接聽  拒接
抱歉  我現在不能接電話
待會兒給你回電
我在工作  待會兒回電
自定義消息
取消
我得請你把這個關掉
I'm gonna have to ask you to switch that off for now.
好的  謝謝
Okay, thanks.
關機
取消
你知道這像什么嗎  有點像過山車
You know what it's kinda like? It's kinda like a rollercoaster.
明白嗎  就像過山車
You know what I mean? It's like a roller coaster.
試試  跟我一起試試
Try it, try it with me.
澳大利亞
曼谷
邊防部隊
印度
歡迎你
迪拜
西班牙
羅馬
我愛巴黎
倫敦眼有多高
How tall-- how tall is the Eye?
大本鐘有多高
How tall-- how tall is Big Ben?
索尼婭
好吧
All right.
配對成功
烏鴉酒館
后來  我就做了兩年的
Since then, I've been working as a technology correspondent
科技記者  感覺很棒
for about two years now. It's been great.
真不錯
Cool, that's awesome.
那你是做電視報道的嗎  就像...
So you do, like, TV reports and, like, you're like...
-不  只在網上播  -只在網上播
- No, just the website. - Oh, just the website?
有一些小視頻什么的
I mean, there's some video stuff,
但主要都是技術產業方面的
but tech industry pieces mainly.
厲害  技術人員  技術很厲害  技術...
Cool, tech-tech. Tech's awesome. Tech's--
那你迄今為止都去過哪
So where have you been so far?
像印第安納·瓊斯一樣周游世界嗎
Travelling around the map like Indiana Jones?
-是啊  -你的冒險之路
- Yeah. - Where the adventure line goes
蜿蜒遍布全世界
zigzagging all over the place.
其實  我差不多游完了...
Yeah, actually, I'm almost done.
但我先飛到悉尼  然后去泰國
But I started off, flew into Sydney, went to Thailand.
-好嫉妒你  -印度  沒錯
- Oh, jealous. - India. Yeah.
去過羅馬  走過羅馬
Did Rome, went to Rome.
-假期逛遍了整個歐洲  -連我都沒走遍
- Did the whole Europe vacation. - Even I haven't done that.
真的嗎
Oh, really?
特別棒  我去了西班牙的潘普洛納
It was awesome. I went to Pamplona in Spain.
-那里是不是會賽牛  -我和牛賽跑
- Is that where they do the bull runs? - Ran with the bulls.
-你和牛賽跑  -我和牛賽跑
- You ran with the bulls? - I ran with the bulls.
-所以才有了這道疤  -瞧啊
- That's how I got this. - Look at that!
你真的和印第安納·瓊斯一樣
You really are Indiana Jones.
你是不是還有帽子  包里還有皮鞭
Have you got your whip in your bag and your hat?
我從納粹手里拯救了世界  可厲害了
I saved the world from the Nazis. That was pretty cool.
我...只是想
I, you know, just... trying to do,
做些我從沒做過的事
you know, shit I've never done before.
這就是你這趟旅行的目的嗎
Is that what you're doing on this trip?
你是要找尋自我嗎
You're, like, finding yourself?
是啊  可以這么說  我...
Yeah, um... in a way. I mean, I--
其實是想離開家一段時間
really to get away from the family home is what I'm doing.
是啊  那...
Yeah, that was--
算了  太無聊了
Whatever, that's boring.
是啊  要就冒險而言
Yeah, well, I'm afraid Britain's pretty tame
英國其實也挺無聊的
as far as Daredevil opportunities go.
是嗎  沒關系  這是我的最后一站了
Yeah? It's alright, it's the last leg of the trip anyway so...
遺憾的是...我下周就要回家了
I'm... unfortunately home next week.
-沒多少時間...  -下周
- Not much time-- - Next week?
是啊
Yeah.
時間不多了
That's not very long.
的確不多
No, it's not.
那...你可以給點建議  什么比較好玩
So... I could use some suggestions on fun shit to do.
-好玩的東西  -好玩的東西
- Fun shit to do? - Fun shit to do.
天啊
Jesus!
你好
Hello.
-早上好  -早上好
- Good morning. - Good morning.
又一道戰斗傷痕
Another battle scar.
算是吧
Kind of.
我猜猜  你當時
Let me guess, you were, like,
在開普敦和鯊魚搏斗  兄弟
totally shark fishing in Cape Town, dude.
你模仿美國口音只能到這種程度嗎
Is that your best American accent?
-是啊  -其實挺像的  那個...
- Yes. - That's pretty good. No, um...
是高中的混蛋喬西·彼得斯留下的紀念
It was courtesy of Josh Peters, high school dick.
他跟我在手藝上打了起來
He and I got into a fight in shop class.
他用個什么金屬棍打了我
And he hit me with this, like, metal rod thing.
真是個混蛋
What an arsehole.
"真是個混蛋"
-口音太爛了  -對不起
- That's terrible. - I'm sorry.
你的還是我的
Is that you or me?
肯定是你的
Oh, it's gotta be you.
"媽媽"  你可真是不折不扣的美國人
"Mom." You're so American.
沒錯
Yes, I am.
媽媽來電
抱歉  我現在不能接電話
待會兒給你回電
我在工作  待會兒回電
自定義消息
取消
你不接嗎
Are you not gonna get that?
這可有點不近人情了
Okay, that was a little impersonal.
怎么  你現在想和她聊聊嗎
What, you wanna talk to her now?
你想和我媽媽聊聊嗎
You wanna talk to my mum?
-我打回去  -你贏了
- I'll call back. - Fair point.
我想也是
I don't think so.
你餓了嗎
You hungry?
瞧瞧這些游戲  你還真是游戲發燒友
Wow, look at all these games. You're, like, a gamer.
酷啊
Cool.
當然了  為了工作
Of course I am. For my job.
怎么了  打《街霸》時沒被妹子干翻過嗎
What, a girl never beat you at Street Fighter?
奇點
這是你的約會手冊嗎
Is this-- Like, this is, like, your dating manual?
什么  《奇點》嗎
What? The Singularity?
講述的是電腦學會智商碾壓男人
It's when computers learn to outsmart man
女人早做到了
like women did years ago.
我之前說的其實是開玩笑的
See, what I was doing, it was like a joke.
-你知道嗎  -真的嗎
- You know? - Really?
-是啊  -這就是你們對開玩笑的定義
- Yeah. - Well, that's what you call a joke?
你們也有"開玩笑"一說吧
Yeah, you guys have those.
你們這里也有吧
You guys have those here, right?
是啊  我們現在就開玩笑
Yeah, yeah. We do at the moment.
這個玩笑不錯  這個玩笑不錯
That was a good joke. That was a good joke.
享用你的馬麥醬吧
Enjoy your Marmite.
天吶
Oh, my...
你們真的吃這鬼玩意嗎
Do you guys seriously eat this shit?
好吧
Okay, alright.
好吧  媽媽救了我一命
Alright, saved by mum.
阻止她再打電話最好的辦法就是...
The best way to actually just stop her from calling is...
我也不知道  接電話吧
I don't know, answer it.
我現在就是不想
Yeah, it's kind of like a can of worms
決開這個堤壩  所以...
I just don't wanna open right now, so...
她在擔心  你是她兒子  你到處旅游
She's worried. You're her son. You've been travelling,
我覺得如果你和她說上幾句  那...
and I just think if you speak to her, then...
我現在還跟她住在一起  在錫拉丘茲
Yeah, well, I still live at home with her back in Syracuse.
-不錯啊  挺好的  -是啊
- That's cool. That's fine. - Yeah.
我之前在照顧我爸爸
I was taking care of my dad.
該死  他...
Oh, shit. Is he...?
-沒事吧  -不  他死了
- ...okay? - No, he died.
-天啊  對不起  -去年的事  沒關系
- Oh, my God. I'm sorry. - Last year. No, it's okay.
我們早知道快了  是早發性阿爾茨海默氏癥
It was coming for a while. It was early onset Alzheimer's.
那肯定很...難熬
Oh, that must have been really... uh... tough.
是啊  他是我最好的朋友
Yeah, he was my best friend.
有時候他看著我  都認不出我是誰了
Sometimes he'd just look at me and wouldn't even know who I was.
我媽媽  我甚至都...
Well, my mum, like, I don't even...
我不知道該怎么和她說話了
I don't know how to talk to her.
我跟她沒有那么親密
You know, I don't have that connection.
我都不知道從什么聊起
I don't even know where to start.
所以我才離開  所以我才開始這趟旅行
So that's why I left. That's why I went on this trip.
只是想暫時逃離
Just to get away
盡量多制造一些回憶
and make, you know, all the memories that I can...
趁我還有能力
while I can.
我知道我終究要跟她說話  我得...
And I know I gotta talk to her and I gotta just...
但不要這樣談  我只是...
But not on this. You know, I just--
我會處理的
I'll deal with it.
等我回去后會處理的  我會...
I'll deal with it when I get back, you know. I'll just...
你是個好人  庫珀
You're a good guy, Cooper.
給你媽媽打電話吧
Call your mum.
卡內余額不足
Zero, zero, one, nine, three, nine, two, nine.
不  我昨晚沒有在蘇梅島買涼鞋
No, I did not buy a pair of sandals in Koh Samui last night
因為我在...
because I'm in--
這要花多久
And how long...and how long does that take?
因為我現在要買機票回美國
Because I need to buy a ticket back to America.
天啊
Oh, my God.
聯系人
媽媽
去電  信息
我要說  這二次約炮的企圖
Can I just say, this is the most blatant cover story
也太明顯了
for a second hook-up ever?
太好了  天啊  謝謝你  謝謝  謝謝
Yes! Yes! Oh, my God. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
好吧  別忘了你的包
Alright. Don't forget your bag.
包  沒錯  我的包
The bag, yep, my bag. Alright.
你是個好姑娘
You are a top bird.
我根本不知道那是什么意思
I don't know what that means,
但我聽別人說過  你就是
but I heard somebody say it once, and you're it.
我有個計劃
I got a plan.
打一些零工
Yeah. It's odd jobs.
-給誰打  -給一個應用
- For who? - For, like, it's an app.
你能  就...
You can kind of-- like...
我沒錢的時候經常用這個  所以...
I've used it all over when funds were low, so...
-的確有些有意思的活兒  -挺不錯的
- Oh, there's some interesting ones. - Pretty cool.
"招募尋求刺激者"
"Thrillseekers wanted."
-這看上去很合你的胃口  -好吧
- This looks right up your street. - Okay.
好吧  酬勞四星  是個大單子  不錯
Okay, four pound signs. That's a biggie. That's good.
招募尋求刺激者
齋藤游戲團隊
英國  伯克郡
離市中心有點遠
It's a little out of town.
是某種游戲測試  給一個叫齋藤...
And some kind of play test deal for a company called Saitoo...
齋藤游...
Saitogoo...
-齋藤游戲  -齋藤游戲  沒錯
- SaitoGemu? - SaitoGemu. Yeah.
那可是個大公司
They're huge.
-真的很大  -真的嗎
- They're really big. - Really?
恐怖游戲
Horror games?
你聽說過...
Have you heard of...
哪個是他們出的來著
oh, what's one of theirs?
《哈萊克魅影》
Harlech Shadow.
《哈萊克魅影》  聽說過
Harlech Shadow? Yes, I have.
我大概七年級的時候在我哥們路德維格的
I used to play that in my buddy David Ludwig's basement
地下室里玩過
when we were, like, seventh grade.
齋藤翔  懼怕他
那就是齋藤翔  是他的公司
Well, that's Shou Saito. It's his company.
-他是個天才  超級神秘  -好吧
- He's like this genius, super secretive. - Okay.
他們在研究一個新項目
And apparently, they're working on this new project.
投了好大一筆錢  前所未有的突破
Big money involved. Groundbreaking.
但沒人知道具體是什么
But nobody knows anything about it.
要是我做得夠好
Well, maybe if I play my cards right
說不定能給你搞到翔的獨家新聞
I can get you an exclusive with Shou.
《翔記》  怎么樣
Fo Shou? Yeah?
你應該拍張照
You should take a photo.
說真的  要是你能拍到
Seriously, if you get a photo of
他們正在研究的任何東西
anything that they're working on,
賺的錢可比四星酬勞多多了
that's a fuckload more money than four pound signs.
好吧
Cool.
這地方到底在哪里
Well, where is this place?
科珀先生
Mr. Copper.
叫我庫珀就行
Just Cooper.
庫珀先生  對不起
Mr. Cooper, I apologize.
就叫我庫珀吧
Just Cooper is fine.
齋藤游戲
既然如此  叫我凱蒂就行了
Then, in that case, I'm just Katie.
-跟我來  -好
- Follow me. - Oh, yeah.
-我拿一下我的行李  -拉弗會處理好的
- I'll just get my pack here. - Rav will take care of that.
拉弗會處理  那好吧
Oh, Rav will take care of that. Okay, great.
好吧  我反正也不想背了
That's good. I don't wanna carry it anyway.
拉弗看上去像最終關卡里的首領怪
Rav kind of reminds me of like an end-of-level boss.
元氣功
You know, haiukon. Just...
-一路過來怎么樣  -挺好的  謝謝
- How was your journey? - Great. Thanks.
-車子順利接到你了嗎  -是的
- The car pick you up okay? - Yeah.
這邊走
This way.
他們...看得到嗎
Are they... seeing?
真厲害  很厲害
It's cool. Very cool.
過來吧
Come on.
感覺我就要見鄧布利多了
Feel like I'm gonna go meet Dumbledore.
希望能分到格蘭芬多
Hope I get Gryffindor.
我要拿走你的電話
I'm gonna need your phone
以及其他能發送和接受訊號的工具
and anything else you might use to send and receive.
-有點疑神疑鬼了吧  -小心駛得萬年船
- A little paranoid, don't you think? - Can't be too careful.
好吧  給你
Okay, there you go.
你還真是疑神疑鬼
Wow, you really are paranoid.
還真白
It's white.
齋藤游戲
我猜這上面是說
Okay, so I'm guessing this says, like,
我同意被采集腎臟嗎
I agree to have my kidneys harvested?
其實是標準保密協議和免責聲明之類的
Actually, it's a pretty standard NDA-disclaimer thing.
好吧
Okay.
重要的是要告訴你
It's important that you realize
我們需要做個小手術
there is a small medical procedure involved.
抱歉  為了測試游戲嗎
Sorry, for a game?
沒有永久性后遺癥  我們也不會取走你的腎
Nothing permanent and we don't harvest your kidneys,
-我保證  好吧
- I promise. - Okay.
比打耳洞造成的傷害都要小
It's no more invasive than having your ears pierced.
"機密信息
"Confidential information,
大腦下載游戲  持續期  中止..."
brain downloads the game, duration, termination..."
簽名頁...
The signature page...
我簽在哪里
Where do I sign?
-要簽名  -少了一頁
- Signature. Yeah. - There's a page missing.
-好吧  -稍等
- Okay. - Just a moment.
好吧  我就等...在這里
Alright. I'll just wait... here.
什么東西
What the fuck?
索尼婭
-顯然還要動手術  -搞什么
-沒事吧  -沒事
- All good? - All good.
我們研究的是一種交互式增強現實系統
What we're working on is an interactive augmented reality system.
-就像虛擬現實  -是加在現實之上的層次
- Like VR? - More like layers on top of reality.
好吧
Okay.
-那是什么  -我們叫這個蘑菇
- What's that? - We call this a mushroom.
-像《馬里奧兄弟》里的  -可以這么說
- Like Mario Brothers? - If you like.
你有相應的資質吧
You're qualified to do this, right?
到現在為止我還沒殺過人
I haven't killed anyone yet.
行嗎
May I?
好
Yeah.
好了
All done.
-就這樣  -我跟你說了我很厲害
- That was it? - See, I told you I'm good.
不  別擔心  這不是永久性的
No, don't worry, it's not permanent.
好吧  這是什么
Okay. What is this, like,
某種記憶測試之類的嗎
some kind of memory test or something like that?
-到時候就知道了  -好吧
- You'll find out. - Oh, okay.
剛啟動的時候你可能會有輕微的刺痛感
You might feel a slight twinge as it initializes.
好吧
Oh, okay.
5點38分開始
Commencing at 5:38.
-你準備好了嗎  -準備好了  長官
- You ready? - Yes, sir!
快好了
Nearly there.
媽媽
來電
我以為我關掉了
I thought I turned that off.
完成了  你感覺還好吧
All done. You feel okay?
好極了
Feel great.
-看這些圓墊  -好的
- Watch the targets. - Okay.
這...
Is--
你看到了什么
What do you see?
像...
Like a-- um--
像一個電子游戲里的地鼠
Like a video game gopher.
-現在是不是更細膩了  -是的
- Is it more detailed now? - Yeah.
沒錯
Yep, yeah.
-現在呢  -我操
- And now? - Holy fuck!
操  它就在...
Holy shit! He-- Fuck. He's right--
它就在...我能...
He's right-- He's right-- Can I--
它不是真的  只是種意識投影
He's not real. He's a sort of mental projection.
-你看得到它  我看不到  -你看不到
- You can see him. I can't. - You can't?
打它一下
Give him a whack.
打它一下  那好吧
Give him a whack? Oh. Okay, alright.
好吧  就像打地鼠一樣
Okay! Alright, so just like whack-a-mole.
我玩過好多次了  好
I've played it a million times. Okay.
好
Alright.
開始吧  來吧
Here we go. Come on up.
你要從哪里出來
Where you coming up?
不  不
No. No.
不
No.
好吧  別出來
Alright. Stay down.
好吧
Okay.
玩得不錯  玩得很不錯  你真可愛
Good game. Very good game. You are so adorable.
好吧  再見  再見
Okay, bye. Bye.
-就這樣嗎  -恐怕是的
- Is that it? - Afraid so.
這些地鼠是二維的還是三維的
Now, were the gophers two-dimensional or three?
三維  不不不  超級三維  就像...
Three. No, no, no. 3D, super 3D. Like-- Yeah.
-這只是部分測試演示  -剛剛只是演示
- Now this is just a limited test demo. - That was a demo?
我覺得你應該進一步
I think you should beta test
測試我們研究的完整體驗
the full experience we're working on.
當然了如果你愿意玩  會給你更多錢
There'd be more money in it, of course. If you're game?
我玩  我玩
I'm game. I'm game.
這位是齋藤翔
This is Shou Saito.
你是新來的志愿測試者吧
You must be our latest volunteer.
這真是太棒了
This is really great.
我想說那個地鼠游戲  超有趣
I just-- I wanted to say that the mole game, super fun.
超有趣  有趣
Super fun... fun.
-有趣  -有趣
- Fun? - Fun.
有趣是好事
Fun is good.
玩游戲很好
Playing games is good.
你的心跳加快
Your heart goes faster.
-你會笑  -是啊
- You smile. - Yeah.
是啊  或者  尖叫
Yeah. Or, um... scream.
《哈萊克魅影》
我一直很喜歡讓玩家跳起來
I have always liked to make the player jump.
驚嚇  你一害怕就會嚇跳起來
Frightened. You get scared, you jump.
-之后  你會感覺很棒  -沒錯
- Afterwards, you feel good. - Yeah.
你會容光煥發
You glow.
為什么呢
Why?
因為腎上腺素的激增
Because of the adrenaline rush.
-沒錯  -是啊
- Yes. - Yeah.
但主要是因為你還活著
But mostly because you are still alive.
你在安全的環境里直面了最深刻的恐懼
You have faced your greatest fears in a safe environment.
這是恐懼的釋放  讓你解放了
It is a release of fear. It liberates you.
是啊  說得太對了
Yeah. I mean, totally.
我們現在研究的
What we are working on now
是有史以來最個人化的恐怖生存游戲
is the most personal survival horror game in history.
厲害
Cool.
利用你自己的思維來嚇你
One that works out how to scare you by using your own mind.
那...聽上去很瘋狂
That-- That sounds crazy.
迫不及待了
Can't wait!
我在上傳神經網絡軟件包
I'm uploading a neural net package.
神經網絡軟件包  神經網絡
Neural net packing, neural net.
你們應該再改進下名字  這名字太過時了
Name could use a little work, I think. It's all 90s.
我開玩笑的  名字不錯
I'm just kidding, it's a good name.
這是最尖端的智能軟件
It's state of the art intelligence software.
它會在運行過程中學習和適應
It learns and adapts on the fly.
它會監控你的腦活動
It'll monitor your brain activity
推斷出最能嚇到你的方式
and try and work out how best to frighten you
然后根據你的體驗進行調整
and then adjust to your experience accordingly.
-你準備好了嗎  -好了
- Are you ready? - Oh, yeah.
《星際迷航》梗
傳送我吧  開始吧  準備發射
Beam me up. Here we go, lock and load.
請閉眼
Eyes closed.
-現在時間為下午6點17  -好
- Time is currently 6:17 p.m. - Okay.
上傳中  五  四  三  二  一
It's uploading. Five, four, three, two, one.
你感覺如何
How are you feeling?
很好  一切正常
I feel good. I feel normal.
好  慢慢站起來
Okay. Stand up, slowly.
你準備好玩游戲了嗎
Are you ready to play?
這不是《哈萊克魅影》的宅子嗎
Isn't this the Harlech Shadow house?
是莊園的一部分
It's part of the estate.
其實是守門人的小屋  但這就是原型
The gamekeeper's lodge, actually. But, yeah, this was the model.
我們為游戲復刻了陳設  掃描了結構
The layout was replicated for the game and the texture scanned.
實在是太酷了
Very, very cool.
游戲怎么玩  我該做什么
So what's the game, what do I do?
你什么都不用做
You don't have to do anything.
你只需獨自待在這里
You just stay in here alone,
看你在害怕得撐不下去之前能堅持多久
see how long you last until you're too scared to continue.
我只需要待在這里
So all I have to do is, like, stay here?
然后就能拿到報酬
And I get paid for that?
我會在控制室里觀察你
I'll be back in the control room, watching.
到處都是攝像頭  不準偷東西哦
There are cameras all over, so no stealing the silverware.
還有這個
And now there's this.
-好  這是什么  -是耳機
- Ok. And what's this? - It's an earpiece.
放進耳朵里
Yeah, just pop it in,
這樣我們就能隨時聯系了
and you and I will be in contact the whole time.
真酷
Oh, cool.
-要是我跟你說話  你就能聽見  -對
- And I can, like, talk to you, and you'll hear it? - Right.
真棒
Great, great, that's great.
你看到的東西都無法真正傷害你
Now, nothing you'll see can physically harm you.
都是視聽虛擬的  就像打地鼠一樣
It's all just audio-visual, like the gopher game.
好的
Oh, okay.
但如果太過激烈  我們可以隨時把你撤出來
But if it does get too intense, we can pull you out at any time
-叫停實驗  -好
- and stop the experiment. - Okay.
你能想到什么安全詞嗎
Is there a safe word you can think of?
遇險時容易想起來的詞
Something easy to remember in distress?
"停"這個詞怎么樣
How about the word "Stop"?
-選得好  就"停"了  -好
- Good choice. "Stop" it is. - Yeah.
好  就讓你獨自享受夜晚吧
Okay, we'll leave you to enjoy your evening.
-好  -我過會兒就會聯系你
- Alright. - You'll hear from me in a moment.
隨意點兒
Just make yourself at home.
好的  悠著點
Okay, all right. Well, take her easy.
哈萊克...魅影
Harlech... Shadow.
是真的嗎  是真的  它真的死了
Is this real? Yeah, it's real. That's real. It's really dead.
庫珀
Cooper.
-你能聽見嗎  -一清二楚
- Are you hearing me? - Loud and clear.
我看見你已經開始借酒壯膽了呢
Reaching for the Dutch courage already, I see.
-但那酒恐怕是不含酒精的  -真差勁
- I'm afraid that wine's non-alcoholic. - Lame.
我們需要你頭腦清醒
Well, we need you with a clear head.
好吧  有道理  有道理
Okay. Fair point. Fair point.
這工藝真精良  真漂亮
This is high-quality craftsmanship. This is nice.
是啊  木工活兒很精致
Yeah. It's good woodwork.
-畫的就是這里  -觀察力滿分
- That's this place. - Full marks for observation.
好了
Alright, there we go.
-糟了  -怎么了
- Oh, shit. - What's up?
我剛才忘了我沒帶手機
I just forgot I don't have my phone.
我一直去拿它  忘了它不在兜里
I keep going for it, I forget it's not in my pocket.
而且這里沒有電視  所以...
And there's, uh... no TV here, so...
歡迎回到19世紀
Welcome to the 19th century.
沒有電視  沒有因特網  沒有無線網絡
No TV, no Internet, no Wi-Fi.
是啊  難怪人們會看到亂七八糟的東西
Yeah. No wonder people were seeing shit.
大概只是因為無聊透頂了吧
Probably were just bored out of their gourds.
這是解釋鬧鬼的主流理論
Well, that's the leading theory about ghost sightings.
大腦受刺激較少時  會產生幻覺
The mind plays tricks when less stimulated.
讓人分心的東西越少  人們就越常看見鬼
Fewer distractions, people saw more ghosts.
知道這個真是太好了
Isn't that a nice piece of info?
但他們有文學作品可讀
Well, they got literature, though.
《鬼故事集》
真貼心
That's pretty sweet, right?
天啊
Oh, my God,
我都不記得上次看書是什么時候了
I can't remember the actual last time that I read a book.
《烏鴉》
想想看  人們曾經故意去看書
To think people used to do this on purpose.
是啊  真是瘋了  何必呢
I know. Crazy. Why?
-我覺得我不該  -安靜  好嗎
- You know, I don't think I've-- - Shh, alright?
我得沉浸在這老式的活動中了  集中注意力
I need to get into some old-school shit here. Concentrate.
抱歉
Pardon me.
我想說  你剛剛心率加快了
Can I point out your heart rate just increased?
當然會了  因為這兒有只特大的蜘蛛
Yeah. Well, it should have cos there's a huge crazy spider.
你看見了一只蜘蛛
You see a spider?
-你看不見它  -看不見
- You don't-- you don't see that? - No.
別爬過來  別
Don't-- don't walk. Don't--
見鬼
Holy shit!
你這樣的壯漢竟然怕蜘蛛
Tough guy like you, scared of spiders.
我只是不喜歡它們
Yeah, I'm just not fond of them.
-你有蜘蛛恐懼癥所以才會嚇到  -天啊
- It's worked out you're an arachnophobe quickly. - My God.
它在尋找弱點
It's probing for weak spots.
該死
God damn it.
混蛋
Fucker!
棒
Yeah!
好吧
Okay.
Yeah, well, yeah.
比打地鼠可真實多了
Whole lot more realistic than the gopher game.
真厲害  圖像處理做得好
It's good. It's good graphics.
挺好的
It's good, uh-- Yeah.
第一時間下載無刪減美劇  必須登錄字幕組網站
真沒勁
Weak sauce.
更好更快的原創翻譯 雙語字幕
-怎么了  -只是
- What is it? - Just--
沒事  沒事
Nothing. Nothing.
我在看畫  有個...不  畫上亮了盞燈
Here with the figures. There's a-- No. There's a light on...
這里面...
now, in the...
你能推進鏡頭嗎
Can you... zoom in and-- zoom in on it?
然后就能看見我在說什么了
And you can see what I'm talking about.
-庫珀...  -現在有個...
- Cooper... - And now there's--
窗戶里有個人  那不是...
There's a guy in the window. That wasn't...
是吧
Yeah.
現在他消失了  窗戶里沒人了
And now he's gone. Now nobody's in the window.
這...
Which is the-- -
嗯  有...
Yeah, there's a--
管子漏水而已
Just leaky pipes.
我就知道  是管子漏水
I knew it. It was leaky pipes, like--
見鬼
Holy fuck!
操
Fuck!
好吧
Okay.
真嚇到我了  你嚇到我了
That got me. You got me.
你看見什么了
What are you seeing?
有個瘆人的家伙
Like a creepy fucking guy.
天啊...
Just...
天啊  天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
他有點像喬西·彼得斯
He kinda looks like Josh Peters.
-喬西·彼得斯  你是喬西·彼得斯  -什么
- It's Josh Peters! You're Josh Peters! - Sorry?
你是高中的喬西·彼得斯
You're Josh Peters from high school!
是我高中認識的人
From a guy I know at high school.
系統為了建構
The system could be mining
可能在挖掘你的部分記憶
some of your personal memories for texture.
喬西·彼得斯是你害怕的人嗎
Was Josh Peters someone you were scared of?
他是個惡霸  我不怕
He was a bully. I wasn't scared.
我不怕他  但他是個惡霸而且
I wasn't scared of him, but he was a bully and--
天啊  上幾節以色列格斗術課
Man! Take a couple of Krav Maga classes
我就準備好了
and I'd be ready.
就準備好了
I'd be ready!
破壞神
Kali ma!
我去喝點酒  再戰
I'm gonna get some wine. Re-up.
我也想給你倒點  但你大概喝不了  所以
I'd offer you some, but I don't think you can drink it so...
過會兒見  彼得斯
Catch ya later, Peters.
這無酒精的酒真棒
This non-alcoholic wine is pretty good.
我不是什么專家  但它很好喝
I'm not like a expert or anything, but it's kinda great.
我去法國的時候  在葡萄園待過
I was in France. I stayed at this, like, vineyard,
他們的一個踩葡萄節上有種酒
and they had this wine, like, grape-stomping festival.
那酒可真好喝  我確定
Now that, that wine was good. I know that.
你在東拉西扯
You're being discursive.
-什么是東拉西扯  -絮絮叨叨
- What is discursive? Discursive? - Talkative.
語無倫次
Rambling.
這是問題嗎
Is that a problem?
人們害怕時  話會變多
People sometimes talk more when they're afraid.
有助于補償恐懼
Helps compensate for the fear.
-同時也是掩飾  -是嗎
- Masks it, too. - Oh, yeah?
類似于你在深夜時打開電視
Similar to when you've got the TV on late at night.
聲音能讓你不那么孤獨
The voices make you feel less alone.
哪怕你確實是一個人
Even though you are alone.
你嚇不到我的  凱蒂
You aren't scaring me, Katie.
可惜了
Pity.
這里有冰箱嗎
Is there like a refrigerator here?
壁櫥里有些零食
There's some snacks in the cupboard.
好的  讓我瞧瞧
Alrighty. Eenie meenie, miney...
找到了
Mo! Alright.
姜味脆餅
Okay, ginger snaps.
看看
Let's see.
這就可以
This'll do.
現在...
Now...
我關門的時候他肯定就在后面  是不是
He's gonna be right behind this door when I close it, isn't he?
對  就是這樣的
Yeah, that's how this works.
我就知道  突然嚇人已經過時了
Knew it. Jump scares get pretty old--
操
Fuck!
天啊
Oh, God.
-那他媽是什么  -你看見什么了
- What the hell is that? - What do you see?
見鬼
Holy shit!
一個該死的...
A fucking--
很難描述
Hard to explain.
是個大號的蜘蛛
It's like a huge-ass spider
有張臉  屌從嘴里伸出來
with a face and dicks coming out of his mouth.
是...
It's...
彼得斯  彼得斯在里面
Peters. Peters is inside.
像是彼得斯和蜘蛛的結合體
Like a Peters-spider mash-up.
凱蒂  這是你干的  還是我
Ah, Katie! Are you doing this, or is this fucking me?
全都是你
I think that's all you.
我真是被害慘了
I'm so fucked up!
天啊  操
God! Fuck!
見鬼  你真是太惡心了
Holy shit, you're fucking gross.
喂
Yeah--
抱歉  你能再說一遍嗎
Sorry, can you say again?
凱蒂  喂
Katie, hello?
該死  凱蒂
Damn it, Katie!
你再上線的時候  說句話就行
Whenever you come back online, just say the word.
我不害怕  就是...無聊而已
No, I'm not scared, just... bored.
是你們嗎
That you guys?
進來修耳機嗎  這主意還不錯
Coming to fix the earpiece? That's probably a good idea.
來了  來了
Yeah. Yeah.
操
Fuck it, man!
來吧
Come on!
你有危險
You're in danger.
索尼婭
Sonja?
這才像話  這真是太不可思議了
Now we're talking. Alright, this is incredible.
真是太了不起了  我服得五體投地
This-- very impressive. I am thoroughly impressed.
我真是...
I am--
你看上去太真了  你簡直和她一模一樣
You look so real. You're, like, just like her.
真的
I mean, wow.
不過  很可惜你不是
Except... you're just unfortunately not...
-庫珀  你在干什么  -等下  慢著
- Cooper, what are you doing? - Wait, wait. Hold on, hold on.
-庫珀  你有危險  -別說話  我得思考
- Cooper, you're in danger. - Quiet. Quiet! I need to think.
你他媽太真了  你是真的  真的
You're fucking real. You are real. You're real.
-庫珀  你  -你是索尼婭  你真在這兒
- Cooper, you're in-- - You're Sonja. You're actually here.
-你真在這兒嗎  -我是真的  我在這兒
- Are you actually here right now? - I'm real. I'm actually here.
-天啊  -我們必須走
- God. - And we have to go.
-你必須聽我說  -你怎么來了
- You have to listen to me. - How are you here?
你記得你給我發的照片嗎
You know that photo that you sent me?
我四處調查  發現齋藤翔去年獲得了一項
I dug around and apparently Shou Saito took out a patent
電腦人腦接口專利
for a computer brain interface last year.
你怎么可能是真的  我不...
How are you real? I don't--
好吧  操  我不...
Okay, fuck. I don't--
他們帶你來的
They brought you here!
你是真的  是他們帶你來的
You are, you're real, and they brought you here,
他們是想耍我  想得美  想得美
and they're trying to fuck with me. Nice try, good try.
我懂了  這是測試的一部分
I get it. It's part of the test.
他的專利被直接拒絕了
His patent got rejected outright.
人們說它瘋狂又危險
They said it was insane, it was dangerous.
真的嗎  他們付給你多少錢
Really? How much are they paying you?
說真的  因為你現在演得太好了
Honestly. Cos you're killing it right now.
他們給你吃了什么嗎
Have they given you something?
抱歉  我還以為你是假的
Sorry, I thought you were fake.
但我現在知道你是真的了
But now I know you're real,
我這主人當得太差勁了
I'm being a really terrible host.
我有無酒精的酒  喝點酒心情可能會好起來
I got some non-alcoholic wine. Might put us in the mood.
庫珀  我想帶你...
Cooper, what I want to do is get you--
我們進廚房說
We'll talk about it in the kitchen.
-庫珀  -索尼婭  別緊張好嗎
- Cooper! - Sonja, relax, okay?
別鬧了  我知道  被我看穿了  別裝了
Give it up. I know, the jig's up, okay? Let it go.
庫珀  還有別的隱情
Look, Cooper, there's more.
去年一年就有五個人失蹤了
Five people have disappeared in the past year.
全都是旅客
All tourists,
都在那個破零工應用上注過冊
all registered with that stupid odd jobs app.
是嗎  天啊  太瘋狂啦
Oh, yeah? Wow. God, that's crazy.
不管他們在對你做什么  對你做了什么
Whatever they're doing to you, whatever they've done to you,
都很危險  我們必須馬上離開  庫珀
it's dangerous, and we really have to go now, Cooper.
好吧  好吧  那好
Okay, okay. Alright.
-如果你的說法是真的  -庫珀
- Well, if your story's true... - Cooper.
-那你是怎么找到我的  -什么
- then how'd you find me? - What?
你怎么知道我在哪
How'd you know where I am?
這是家游戲公司  我查了地址
It's a games company, I looked up the address.
真的嗎
Yeah, really?
不對  你是怎么找到這的  就這里
No, no, no, no. How'd you find me here? This place.
-我追蹤了你  -追蹤了我
- I tracked you. - You tracked me?
就通過"找朋友"功能查你手機的衛星定位
Yeah, with your GPS on your phone. Find My Friends.
"找朋友"
Find My Friends?
被你圓回來了  但他們帶走了我的手機
That would've worked, but they took my phone.
而手機在好幾里地外的建筑里  露餡了吧
And it's in a building, like, a mile away. So, yeah, nice try.
就這樣
That's right.
還說女人智商碾壓男人  奇點一下吧
So much for women outsmarting men. Singularity that!
我只是想說
Look, all I'm saying is that
我覺得你們可以再把故事編得好一些
I think that you could've come up with a better story,
這樣才有趣...
it could have been funny or...
好吧  你別生氣啊
Okay, alright, don't be pissed.
你有沒想過你的銀行賬戶是怎么被黑的
Do you ever wonder how your bank account got hacked?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
-你睡著的時候我復制了你的卡  -好吧
- I cloned your card as you were asleep. - Okay.
把刀放下  你拿刀干什么
Put the knife down. What are you going to do with that?
是我讓你注意到了這個工作
I drew your attention to this job.
索尼婭  把刀放下好嗎  這不好玩
Sonja, put the fucking knife down, okay? It's not funny.
你應該打給你媽  庫珀
Should've called your mum, Cooper.
-但是你聯系了我    -索尼婭
- But you called me...  - Sonja.
我又引你來到了這里
and I led you here...
-聽我說  -就像面包屑引路
- You know what? - ...like a breadcrumb trail.
把刀放下  別演了
Put the knife down. Drop the act.
說真的  把刀放下  索尼婭
Okay, seriously, drop the knife, Sonja.
這他媽不好玩了  把刀放...
It's not fucking funny. Put the knife...
我可不是來挨刀子的  我受夠了好嗎
This isn't what I signed up for. I'm fucking done, okay?
我去
Fuck!
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
我去
Oh, fuck!
我了個天
Holy fuck!
停
Stop!
我操
Fuck!
操  操
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck!
-庫珀  -凱蒂
- Cooper. - Katie!
-凱蒂  -庫珀
- Katie! - Cooper.
-凱蒂  -庫珀  怎么回事
- Katie! - Cooper, what's happening?
這他媽搞什么鬼
What the fuck happened?
發生什么了
What's happening?
我們在呼叫你  你一直不回話
We've been talking. You've not been responding.
你不是說我什么都感覺不到嗎
You said I wouldn't feel anything!
你看到什么了  出現什么了
What are you seeing? What's there?
-我操  但是她不見了  -誰不見了
- Fuck! She's gone now. - Who's gone?
我的天  我都感覺到了
Oh, my God, I... I felt it.
我胳膊上被捅了把刀子
There's a knife in my arm!
-就肩膀上  -庫珀  你看見誰了
- In my shoulder. - Cooper, who was there?
-媽的...索尼婭  -誰
- Fuck... Sonja. - Who?
索尼婭  是我認識的一妞
Sonja. She's this girl that I know,
她媽逼的捅了我
that fucking- -  She stabbed me.
-她還拿了把刀  -你不會受傷的  庫珀
- She had a fucking knife. - Nothing can harm you, Cooper.
-不不不  我摸得到她  -那不可能
- No, no, no, no. She was solid. - No, she can't have been.
她...我被捅了  我還不知道嗎
She- -  I was stabbed! I would know!
你看見的一切事物都不會觸碰或傷害到你
Nothing you see can harm or even touch you.
只是純粹的視聽效果
It's purely audio- visual.
-不會有體感的  -操  怎么沒體感
- There's no physical sensation. - Fuck! Yes, there was!
庫珀你得冷靜下來
Cooper, you need to calm down.
我都感覺到了好嗎
I know because I felt it, okay?
我感覺到了她的胳膊  還有體溫
I felt her arm, it was warm,
我還感覺到她捅了我肩膀一刀
and I felt her fucking stab me in the shoulder.
-這不可能  -我的天
- That's not possible. -  Oh, my God.
-這不可能啊  庫珀  -是真的  真的
- It's not possible, Cooper. - Yeah, it is! Yeah, it is!
身體應該是沒有任何感覺的
Physical sensations shouldn't be possible.
-除非  -我的天  除非什么
- Unless, I mean... - Oh, God. Unless what?
我不知道  神經網絡也許通過某種機制
I don't know. The neuron net, it could have maybe worked out
創造出了體感知覺
some means of replicating physical experiences,
-但這是前所未有的事  -我的天
- but that would be unprecedented. - Jesus Christ.
我告訴你  馬上停止游戲
Okay, you know what? Stop the game.
我不干了  把我撤出去
I want out. Just pull me out now.
停停停  聽見安全詞了嗎  媽的快停
Stop, stop, stop. Safe word. Fucking stop!
-好了  讓我們想個辦法  -我的天
- Okay, okay, just let us work it out. - Oh, God.
不行  我現在就把這玩意挖出來
No, I want this fucking thing out now.
庫珀  千萬不要自己動手拔出來
Cooper, do not attempt to remove that yourself.
自行移除設備危險性非常大
Removing it yourself is extremely dangerous.
停下  你會死的
Stop that, that could kill you!
冷靜
Just stay calm!
那是翔嗎
Is that Shou?
是翔嗎  他說什么  他在說什么
Is that Shou? What's he saying? What's he saying?
好了庫珀  我們要啟動退出程序了
Okay, Cooper. We're gonna commence with deactivation.
真是太好了
Oh, that's great news.
我們需要你服從指令
We need you to follow instructions
到達接入點
and make it to the access point.
接入點  好極了  這個破接入點在哪
The access point? Great. Where the fuck's the access point?
-我操還要爬樓  拜托  -最后一層了
- Oh, fuck! More stairs? Come on! - Just one more level.
-相信我  -好吧
- Trust me. - Okay.
頂層左轉
Left at the top.
-哪扇門  -盡頭的房間
- Okay, which door? - Room at the end.
怎么了
What is it?
里面有很不好的東西  我能感覺到
There's gonna be something bad in there. I can feel it.
-就像是...  -什么
- Something like... - Like what?
私人的什么破事
Some personal fucked-up shit.
我能感覺到這玩意在我腦子里打探
Like... I don't know, I could feel it digging around in my head.
庫珀  去開門
Cooper, get to the door.
大概是我媽  或許...死了
It's gonna be like my mum, I don't know, dead.
-你母親  -吊在房梁上
- Your mum? - Fucking swinging from a fucking beam.
-你母親不在里面  -你又控制不了
- Your mother is not in there. - You're not in control of this!
它在我腦子里  它知道的
It's in my head. It fucking knows. It knows.
-它知道  -知道什么
- It knows! - It knows what?
知道我和我媽之間的事
It knows I got this thing with my mum.
庫珀  我保證  你母親不在里面
Cooper, I promise you, she's not in there.
-快開門吧  -我的天啊
- Now open the door. - Oh, my God.
只有這樣我才能接你出來  聽我的
It's the only way I can get you out. Listen to me.
好吧  好
Okay, Okay. Fuck. Okay.
不管房間里有什么都不會傷害你
Whatever's in there cannot harm you.
但你不開門我就沒法讓你退出  庫珀
But I can't get you out unless you open that door, Cooper.
請你快點開門吧
Would you kindly open the door?
開了  開了
Here we go. Here we go.
好吧
Okay.
好了  我進房間了  接入點在哪
Okay, okay, I'm in the room. Where's the access point?
接入點
Access point?
-根本就沒有接入點  -什么
- There is no access point. - What?
我逗你玩呢  庫珀
I'm fucking with you, Cooper.
我讓你爬到這里就是想看你會不會崩潰到
I told you to come up here to see if we've broken you enough
無條件服從命令
to obey instructions without question.
-我們做到了  -不不不
- And we have. - Oh, no, no, no.
凱蒂  別這樣凱蒂  拜托  讓我出去
Katie, come on. Katie, come on, let me out!
凱蒂  讓我出去  搞什么鬼
Katie, let me out, come on! What the fuck!
你要做什么  你要對我做什么
Oh, what are you gonna do? Oh, what are you doing to me?
-你為什么要這么做  -你以為會看見母親
- Why are you doing this? - You thought you'd see your mother.
-操  -她長什么樣
- Oh, fuck! - What does she look like?
你母親  你能形容一下她的相貌嗎
Your mother, can you describe her face?
她的發色什么的
Her hair colour?
她
She...
她高矮胖瘦
Is she tall, short, fat, thin?
-你在哪長大  -她...
- Where did you grow up? - She...
你最喜歡的樂隊  最喜歡的冰淇淋口味
What's your favourite band? Your favourite flavour ice cream?
那個捅了你的女孩的名字
The name of the girl who stabbed you?
你全都想不起來了  是不是
You don't know any of these things, do you?
你不覺得奇怪嗎
Don't you think that's odd?
它把我的記憶奪走了
It's fucking taking my memories!
嚴格來講是覆蓋了
Overwriting them, technically.
看著你身后的鏡子
Look in the mirror behind you.
你還認得你自己嗎
Do you recognize yourself?
你知道鏡子里的人是誰嗎
Do you even know who you're looking at?
很快你就什么都不是了  就像你父親
Soon you won't be anything. You'll be just like your dad.
閉嘴  閉嘴  閉嘴
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
-這才是你最大的恐懼是不是  -閉嘴
- That's what really scares you, isn't it? - Stop it.
-閉嘴  閉嘴  -你就要步他的后塵
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! - You're going the same place he did.
閉嘴  閉嘴  閉嘴
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
-你哪也去不了  -閉嘴  閉嘴
- You're going nowhere. - Shut up! Shut up.
你應該打給你媽  你只有她了
You should have called mum. She's all that's left.
-你拋棄了她  -不不不
- You abandoned her. - No, no, no, no!
滾出我的腦袋
Get out of my head!
-你再也見不到她了  -滾出我的腦袋
- You'll never see her again. - Get out of my fucking head!
你再也不能和她說話了
You'll never speak to her again.
-再也看不到她的臉  -滾出我的腦袋
- Never see her face. - Get out of my fucking head!
滾出我的腦袋  滾出我的腦袋
Get out of my fucking head! Get out of my fucking head!
你個不肖子  你再也見不到你媽了
You're a bad son. You'll never see your mother again.
你哪也去不了
You're going nowhere.
從此湮滅
Straight into oblivion.
你活該  你本來該打給她
You deserve it. You should have called her.
滾出我的腦袋
Get out of my fucking head!
滾出我的腦袋  滾出我的腦袋
Get it out of my head! Get it out of my head!
滾出我的腦袋
Get it out of my fucking head!
庫珀  我這就關上好嗎  我需要鏈接設備
Cooper, I'm gonna shut it off, okay? I just need to connect.
滾出我的腦袋
Get it out of my head!
滾出我的腦袋  滾出我的腦袋
Get it out of my head! Get it out of my head!
我的天啊  我在哪
Oh, my God. Where am I?
你是誰
Who are you?
我關不掉了
I can't stop it.
我不知道我是誰  我得回家
I don't know who I am. So I- -  So I need to go home.
接口的數據線路就像樹根一樣
The interface has data tendrils like roots.
它們本不該插得這么深
They've dug in deeper than they're meant to.
直接穿過了你的大腦
Threaded through your brain,
掌控了所有區域  我無法阻止
taken over whole areas, I can't stop it.
我也無法取出  沒有辦法阻止了
I can't remove it, and I can't stop it.
可是我不知道我是誰
But I- -  But I don't know who I am.
我不知道我是誰
I don't know- -  I don't know who I am.
I don't know who I am.
我全忘了
I don't know.
我謹代表齋藤游戲團隊  向您深表歉意
On behalf of Saito Game Team, I most humbly apologize.
你是誰  你對我做了什么
Who are you? What have you done to me?
-你對我做了什么  -和其他人關在一起吧
- What have you done to me? - Put him with the others, please.
不不不不
No, no, no, no! No, no, no!
停停停停停停停停停
Stop, stop, stop, stop! Stop, stop, stop!
停停停停停  不要  不要
Stop, stop, stop, stop! No, don't, don't!
不要  不要
Don't! Don't!
停  停
Stop! Stop!
不
No!
我了個去
Oh, fuck.
這才一秒
That was one second.
要么是他太容易受影響了
Either he's super susceptible to this
要么就是軟件仍然太過強大
or the software is way too powerful still.
讀數在五毫秒內從0暴漲到18000
It's jumped from zero to 18K in five milliseconds...
我很抱歉  游戲體驗的威力
I'm sorry. The experience
還是大大超出了預期  庫珀先生
was more powerful than intended, Mr. Cooper.
希望您能原諒我們
I hope you can forgive us.
...放置于您前排座椅的下方
...all luggage under the seat in front of you.
即將到達  紐約
請關閉所有電子設備
請關閉并妥善收好所有電子設備
All electronic devices should now be turned off and stowed
以免干擾到
as they may interfere with the
飛機的導航和通訊系統
aircraft's navigational and communication....
媽
Mum?
我得打給他
I have to call him.
媽
Mum?
庫珀為什么要走
Why did Cooper go?
-我  -媽  我就在這里啊
- I...  - Mom, I'm right here. I'm- -
-我就在這兒  媽  -我得聯系庫珀
- I'm right here, Mum. - I have to call Cooper.
必打給他  問問他好不好
I have to call and make sure that he's safe.
我得打給他  我得打給他  我得打給他
I have to call him. I have to call him. I have to call him.
媽
Mum?
Mum!
媽  媽  媽  媽
Mum! Mum! Mum! Mum!
操
Fuck.
媽媽來電
-怎么回事  -他的電話響了
- What happened? - His phone rang.
-你不是把手機收了嗎  -是  但是
- You didn't take it off him? - Yes, but...
-信號被干擾了  -我明明關機了
- The signals interfere. - I know I switched it off.
也許他趁我出去的時候做了什么
Maybe he did something while I was out of the room.
是我疏忽了  我以后一定注意
An oversight. Won't happen again.
傳入信號一定是
The incoming signal must have
干擾了上傳數據流
interfered with the upload sequence.
他大腦中所有的神經突觸同時激活了
Every synapse of his brain lit up at once.
然后就沒反應了  就成那樣了
Then went dead. Like that.
你說他之前在大喊  他喊了什么
You said he shouted something. What was it?
"媽"
"Mum."
-記錄下來  -是
- Make a note of that. - Yes.
庫珀·雷德菲爾德
測試時長  0.04秒
崩潰原因  來電干擾
出現征狀
大喊[打給]"媽"